https://www.shop4lesbians.com/catalog/privacy.php

Search:
Advanced Search
Currencies:
US DollarEuroSchweizer Franken
Languages:
My Account
Cart Contents:0 items
Home
What's New?
Specials
Bestsellers
Contact Us
About us
PRIDE ItemsTOTALLY GIRL POWEREDAccessoriesCar AccessoriesFlagsKey ChainsMagnetsPatchesPinsPostcardsStickersAllPride StickersStandardReflectiveStatic ClingBisexual/TransgenderFairiesPin UpsClassicsTravelGamesPet Supplies.AllCharmsCollarsLeashesPlush AnimalsJewelryBraceletsAllPride BraceletsStainless SteelBeach WearFriendship BraceletsNecklacesAllPride Necklaces/PendantsDog TagsBeach WearAccessoriesRingsAllPride RingsMisc. RingsPiercingsEarringsClothesAccessoriesBagsBeltsHeadgearJackets_HoodiesShirtsShoesSunglassesT-ShirtsLesbian T-ShirtsUnderwearEroticaAllBoys Only ToysGirls Only ToysDildosVibratorsAnalXXX MoviesBooksRestraintsSensualGamesHarnessUsefulSexy edible goodiesDVD / MoviesGay MoviesLesbian MoviesHome&GardenBathroomGardenKitchenInterior_decorationsMisc.Party SuppliesParty DecorationWedding GiftsBachelor/ette Party
What's New?
Ring OHM Zen Spinning Stainless Steel$ 19.71 $ 9.85
Information
Shipping & Returns Payment Methods Privacy Notice Disclaimer About us Contact Us Gift Voucher FAQ
Specials
Lesbian Movie ShowGirls $ 22.41 $ 5.63
Tag Cloud
accessories beads black bracelet bumper button collar dildo earrings fairy family flag girl girls harness heart jacket keychain leather lesbian liebe love magnet mens mobile movie necklace patch pendant phone postcards power pride rainbow ribbon ring rodeoh sexy shoe stainless star steel sticker style symbol tribal underwear vibrator white with
Top » Catalog » Privacy Statement
Privacy Statement
Privacy Policy
Personal data (usually referred to just as "data" below) will only be processed by us to the extent necessary and for the purpose of providing a functional and user-friendly website, including its contents, and the services offered there.
Per Art. 4 No. 1 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679, i.e. the General Data Protection Regulation (hereinafter referred to as the "GDPR"), "processing" refers to any operation or set of operations such as collection, recording, organization, structuring, storage, adaptation, alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination, or otherwise making available, alignment, or combination, restriction, erasure, or destruction performed on personal data, whether by automated means or not.
The following privacy policy is intended to inform you in particular about the type, scope, purpose, duration, and legal basis for the processing of such data either under our own control or in conjunction with others. We also inform you below about the third-party components we use to optimize our website and improve the user experience which may result in said third parties also processing data they collect and control.
Our privacy policy is structured as follows:
I. Information about us as controllers of your dataII. The rights of users and data subjectsIII. Information about the data processing
I. Information about us as controllers of your data
The party responsible for this website (the "controller") for purposes of data protection law is:
Syzzling GmbH
SHOOZIES Network
Fab & Sunci Syz
Oberebenestrasse 21
CH - 5620 Bremgarten
Switzerland
E-Mail: badmail@regenbogenshop.com
The controller's data protection officer is:
Sunci Syz
II. The rights of users and data subjects
With regard to the data processing to be described in more detail below, users and data subjects have the right
to confirmation of whether data concerning them is being processed, information about the data being processed, further information about the nature of the data processing, and copies of the data (cf. also Art. 15 GDPR);
to correct or complete incorrect or incomplete data (cf. also Art. 16 GDPR);
to the immediate deletion of data concerning them (cf. also Art. 17 DSGVO), or, alternatively, if further processing is necessary as stipulated in Art. 17 Para. 3 GDPR, to restrict said processing per Art. 18 GDPR;
to receive copies of the data concerning them and/or provided by them and to have the same transmitted to other providers/controllers (cf. also Art. 20 GDPR);
to file complaints with the supervisory authority if they believe that data concerning them is being processed by the controller in breach of data protection provisions (see also Art. 77 GDPR).
In addition, the controller is obliged to inform all recipients to whom it discloses data of any such corrections, deletions, or restrictions placed on processing the same per Art. 16, 17 Para. 1, 18 GDPR. However, this obligation does not apply if such notification is impossible or involves a disproportionate effort. Nevertheless, users have a right to information about these recipients.
Likewise, under Art. 21 GDPR, users and data subjects have the right to object to the controller's future processing of their data pursuant to Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. In particular, an objection to data processing for the purpose of direct advertising is permissible.
III. Information about the data processing
Your data processed when using our website will be deleted or blocked as soon as the purpose for its storage ceases to apply, provided the deletion of the same is not in breach of any statutory storage obligations or unless otherwise stipulated below.
Server data
For technical reasons, the following data sent by your internet browser to us or to our server provider will be collected, especially to ensure a secure and stable website: These server log files record the type and version of your browser, operating system, the website from which you came (referrer URL), the webpages on our site visited, the date and time of your visit, as well as the IP address from which you visited our site.
The data thus collected will be temporarily stored, but not in association with any other of your data.
The basis for this storage is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. Our legitimate interest lies in the improvement, stability, functionality, and security of our website.
The data will be deleted within no more than seven days, unless continued storage is required for evidentiary purposes. In which case, all or part of the data will be excluded from deletion until the investigation of the relevant incident is finally resolved.
Cookies
a) Session cookies
We use cookies on our website. Cookies are small text files or other storage technologies stored on your computer by your browser. These cookies process certain specific information about you, such as your browser, location data, or IP address.
This processing makes our website more user-friendly, efficient, and secure, allowing us, for example, to display our website in different languages or to offer a shopping cart function.
The legal basis for such processing is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. b) GDPR, insofar as these cookies are used to collect data to initiate or process contractual relationships.
If the processing does not serve to initiate or process a contract, our legitimate interest lies in improving the functionality of our website. The legal basis is then Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR.
When you close your browser, these session cookies are deleted.
b) Third-party cookies
If necessary, our website may also use cookies from companies with whom we cooperate for the purpose of advertising, analyzing, or improving the features of our website.
Please refer to the following information for details, in particular for the legal basis and purpose of such third-party collection and processing of data collected through cookies.
c) Disabling cookies
You can refuse the use of cookies by changing the settings on your browser. Likewise, you can use the browser to delete cookies that have already been stored. However, the steps and measures required vary, depending on the browser you use. If you have any questions, please use the help function or consult the documentation for your browser or contact its maker for support. Browser settings cannot prevent so-called flash cookies from being set. Instead, you will need to change the setting of your Flash player. The steps and measures required for this also depend on the Flash player you are using. If you have any questions, please use the help function or consult the documentation for your Flash player or contact its maker for support.
If you prevent or restrict the installation of cookies, not all of the functions on our site may be fully usable.
Order processing
The data you submit when ordering goods and/or services from us will have to be processed in order to fulfill your order. Please note that orders cannot be processed without providing this data.
The legal basis for this processing is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. b) GDPR.
After your order has been completed, your personal data will be deleted, but only after the retention periods required by tax and commercial law.
In order to process your order, we will share your data with the shipping company responsible for delivery to the extent required to deliver your order and/or with the payment service provider to the extent required to process your payment.
The legal basis for the transfer of this data is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. b) GDPR.
Customer account/registration
If you create a customer account with us via our website, we will use the data you entered during registration (e.g. your name, your address, or your email address) exclusively for services leading up to your potential placement of an order or entering some other contractual relationship with us, to fulfill such orders or contracts, and to provide customer care (e.g. to provide you with an overview of your previous orders or to be able to offer you a wishlist function). We also store your IP address and the date and time of your registration. This data will not be transferred to third parties.
During the registration process, your consent will be obtained for this processing of your data, with reference made to this privacy policy. The data collected by us will be used exclusively to provide your customer account.
If you give your consent to this processing, Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. a) GDPR is the legal basis for this processing.
If the opening of the customer account is also intended to lead to the initiation of a contractual relationship with us or to fulfill an existing contract with us, the legal basis for this processing is also Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. b) GDPR.
You may revoke your prior consent to the processing of your personal data at any time under Art. 7 Para. 3 GDPR with future effect. All you have to do is inform us that you are revoking your consent.
The data previously collected will then be deleted as soon as processing is no longer necessary. However, we must observe any retention periods required under tax and commercial law.
Credit checks and scores
If you accept any offer we make for you to pay for goods or services on account, we reserve the right to run a credit check with a credit bureau (such as Creditreform, Schufa, Bürgel, or infoscore) to obtain credit information determined on the basis of mathematical-statistical methods. For this purpose, any data you provide that is relevant to the contract, such as your name and address, will be forwarded to the credit bureau. We then use the information obtained about the statistical probability of default to decide whether we will offer you payment on account.
The legal basis for such processing is our legitimate interest to avoid default on our account per Art. 6 Para.1 lit. f) GDPR.
Newsletter
If you register for our free newsletter, the data requested from you for this purpose, i.e. your email address and, optionally, your name and address, will be sent to us. We also store the IP address of your computer and the date and time of your registration. During the registration process, we will obtain your consent to receive this newsletter and the type of content it will offer, with reference made to this privacy policy. The data collected will be used exclusively to send the newsletter and will not be passed on to third parties.
The legal basis for this is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. a) GDPR.
You may revoke your prior consent to receive this newsletter under Art. 7 Para. 3 GDPR with future effect. All you have to do is inform us that you are revoking your consent or click on the unsubscribe link contained in each newsletter.
Contact
If you contact us via email or the contact form, the data you provide will be used for the purpose of processing your request. We must have this data in order to process and answer your inquiry; otherwise we will not be able to answer it in full or at all.
The legal basis for this data processing is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. b) GDPR.
Your data will be deleted once we have fully answered your inquiry and there is no further legal obligation to store your data, such as if an order or contract resulted therefrom.
Google-Maps
Our website uses Google Maps to display our location and to provide directions. This is a service provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043 (hereinafter: Google).
Through certification according to the EU-US Privacy Shield
https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active
Google guarantees that it will follow the EU's data protection regulations when processing data in the United States.
To enable the display of certain fonts on our website, a connection to the Google server in the USA is established whenever our website is accessed.
If you access the Google Maps components integrated into our website, Google will store a cookie on your device via your browser. Your user settings and data are processed to display our location and create a route description. We cannot prevent Google from using servers in the USA.
The legal basis is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. Our legitimate interest lies in optimizing the functionality of our website.
By connecting to Google in this way, Google can determine from which website your request has been sent and to which IP address the directions are transmitted.
If you do not agree to this processing, you have the option of preventing the installation of cookies by making the appropriate settings in your browser. Further details can be found in the section about cookies above.
In addition, the use of Google Maps and the information obtained via Google Maps is governed by the Google Terms of Use https://policies.google.com/terms?gl=DE&hl=en and the Terms and Conditions for Google Maps https://www.google.com/intl/de_de/help/terms_maps.html.
Google also offers further information at
https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated
https://policies.google.com/privacy
Google Fonts
Our website uses Google Fonts to display external fonts. This is a service provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043 (hereinafter: Google).
Through certification according to the EU-US Privacy Shield
https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active
Google guarantees that it will follow the EU's data protection regulations when processing data in the United States.
To enable the display of certain fonts on our website, a connection to the Google server in the USA is established whenever our website is accessed.
The legal basis is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. Our legitimate interest lies in the optimization and economic operation of our site.
When you access our site, a connection to Google is established from which Google can identify the site from which your request has been sent and to which IP address the fonts are being transmitted for display.
Google offers detailed information at
https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated
https://policies.google.com/privacy
in particular on options for preventing the use of data.
Model Data Protection Statement for Anwaltskanzlei Weiß & Partner
Continue
Main Manu
Home
Shipping & Returns Payment Methods Privacy Notice Disclaimer About us Contact Us
www.shop4lesbians.com is part of the SHOOZIES Lesbian Network:
Lesbian Community and many more...
Follow us on
Copyright © by SHOOZIES NETWORK
The following link may contain erotic material. To access this area, you need to be at least 18. Are you 18 or older?
